Finding Aid for the John James Tigert IV, Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Subject Entries
  - Nimmons, William
Chronological Entries
1840 - 1849
1850 - 1859
1860 - 1869
1870 - 1879
1880 - 1889
For name entries; see Index of Incoming Correspondence in the Register.